Papers of the National War Labor Board on Microfilm 5752 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Digests of Cases (Reel 22)
  - Tool Makers and Machinists v. Savage Arms et al. Philadelphia, PA, 408 (Reel 22)
  - Motion Picture Exhibitors, Local 1 v. Motion Picture Machine Operators Local 160. Cleveland, 409 (Reel 22)
  - Telephone Operators v. Dakota Central Telephone. Aberdeen, SD, 410 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 395 v. Aetna Foundry et al. Warren, OH., 411 (Reel 22)
  - Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers, Locals 253 and 254 v. Florida Phosphate Mining et al. Mulberry and Fort Meade, FL, 412 (Reel 22)
  - Labor v. Detroit Employers Association. Detroit., 413 (Reel 22)
  - Electrical Workers v. Intermountain Power. Spokane, WA, 414 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Philadelphia Railway. Philadelphia., 415 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 587 v. Puget Sound Traction, Light, and Power et al. Seattle, WA, 416 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees v. Detroit United Railway. Detroit, 417 (Reel 22)
  - Electrical Workers, Local 17 v. Michigan State Telephone. Detroit, 418 (Reel 22)
  - Association of Employing Printers v. Printing Pressmen's and Assistants' Union, Local 23. New York City, 419 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. D.M. Dillon Steam Boiler Works. Fitchburg, MA, 420 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Divisions 721 and 724 v. Lewiston, Augusta, and Waterville Street Railway. Augusta, ME, 421 (Reel 22)
  - Bricklayers' and Masons' Unions v. Whitney and Company. New York City. Employees v. E.W. Bliss. Brooklyn, NY, 422 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Kingston Consolidated Railway. Kingston, NY, 423 (Reel 22)
  - Street and Electric Railway Employees, Division 826 v. San Diego Street Railway. San Diego, 424 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. American Car and Foundry. Berwick, PA, 425 (Reel 22)
  - Boilermakers, Local 295 v. Stacy-Schmidt. York, PA, 426 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Western Knitting Mills. Rochester, MI, 427 (Reel 22)
  - Wage Scale--Nashville Railway and Light. Nashville, TN, 428 (Reel 22)
  - Emergency Employees v. Western Union Telegraph. Kansas City, MO, 429 (Reel 22)
  - Bakers, Local 17 v. Brennan Baking et al. Columbus, OH, 430 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Maryland Pressed Steel. Hagerstown, MD, 431 (Reel 22)
  - Ladies Garment Workers, Local 54 v. Rosenwald and Weil. Chicago, IL, 432 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 210 v. Turner Frick Machine et al. Sharon, PA, 433 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Nonnabo Chemical. Phillipsdale, RI., 434 (Reel 22)
  - Jewelry Workers, Local 8 v. Metal Trades Association. Providence, RI, 435 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Fort Wayne and Northwestern Railway. Waterloo, IN, 436 (Reel 22)
  - Producers' Supply Company v. Molders, Local 119. Franklin, PA, 437 (Reel 22)
  - Steam and Operating Engineers, Local 567 v. Ohio Electric Railway and Power. Zanesville, OH, 438 (Reel 22)
  - Case Hardening Departments v. Employers. Syracuse, NY, 439 (Reel 22)
  - Iron, Steel, and Tin Workers, Local 81 v. Wheeling Steel and Iron. Wheeling, WV, 440 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. Commonwealth Steel. Granite City, IL, 441 (Reel 22)
  - Gas Makers v. Minneapolis Gas Light. Minneapolis, MN, 442 (Reel 22)
  - Molders, Local 11 v. Rochester Foundrymen's Association. Rochester, NY, 443 (Reel 22)
  - Conductors and Motormen v. Union Light and Power. Junction City, KS, 444 (Reel 22)
  - Electrical Workers, Locals 65 and 122 v. Employers. Butte, MT., 445 (Reel 22)
  - Employees v. T.O. and E. Railroad et al. De Queen, AR, 446 (Reel 22)
  - Central Trades Council v. Industrial Works. Bay City, MI, 447 (Reel 22)
  - Inquiry of Gleason Works relative to Introduction, 448 (Reel 22)